

### Anderson Toledo Martins Moreira

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

atmmoreira.ri@amail.com

(a) +55 21 992890362 (b) +55 21 26922032

LINKEDIN: http://br.linkedin.com/in/atmmoreira PORTFOLIO: http://atmdesign.com.br GITHUB: https://github.com/atmmoreira



I'm a Web Designer for over 10 years creating Layouts with Photoshop, Illustrator, HTML5/CSS3, Javascript (jQuery) and Bootstrap. For projects of Institutional Websites, Online Catalogs, and Small Virtual Stores, I use Wordpress with creation of simple themes and implementation of layout in ready themes.

In order to become a Fullstack Javascript Developer, I have been updating on the new features of ECMASCRIPT to deepen my knowledge and make me, master in technologies like: Javascript (Vanilla.js), Node.js (Express), Vue.js, React.js and React Native form mobile apps. In addition learn all ecosystems that involve these technologies, such as MongoDB, Jenkins, Docker, Webpack, etc.

## EXPERIENCES

#### **TIPLAN**

06/2019 - current

#### » Frontend Developer - Rio de Janeiro, Brazil.

I work with Creation Frontend Systems of .Net applications of NFS-e (Electronic Services Invoice), SPE (Electronic City Hall Systems), using SASS, HTML5/CSS3, ¡Query, Bootstrap. Code management and versioning using Team Foundation Server (TFS) and SCRUM Methodology.

#### ATSNET Soluções

09/2018 - 04/2019 **REMOTE** 

#### » Frontend Developer - Rio de Janeiro, Brazil.

Shared Hosting Set-up. Frontend creation of a portal with HTML5/CSS3, jQuery, Bootstrap. Using the Leaflet.js library for georeferencing. Layout diagramming and coding. Maintenance on websites in Wordpress.

#### MediaTrust

12/2017 - 08/2018 **REMOTE** 

#### Frontend Developer - Lisbon, Portugal.

Shared Hosting Set-up. Layout diagramming and coding. UI Design wireframes and mockups translated into responsive and interactive features using HTML5/CSS3, jQuery, Bootstrap and the basic of PHP. Maintenance on websites in Wordpress.

#### LDC comex

11/2015 - 11/2017 **REMOTE** 

#### » Frontend Developer - Rio de Janeiro, Brazil.

Creation Frontend of Systems for .Net Framework applications and tools focused on the customs market. Working with HTML5/CSS3, jQuery and Bootstrap. Layout diagramming and coding. Maintenance on websites in Wordpress.

#### Unigranrio

08/2011 - 10/2015 **REMOTE** 

#### » Frontend Developer - Rio de Janeiro, Brazil.

Conversion of PDF files to HTML5/CSS3, jQuery and Bootstrap. Using Gracefull Degradation technique to harmonize screens. Maintenance on websites in Wordpress.

# EDUCATION •

2008 - 2011

#### TECHNOLOGY OF SYSTEMS FOR INTERNET

UNESA (University Estácio de Sá) - Rio de Janeiro, Brasil

## SKILLS

**BASIC:** ExpressJs » Docker » MongoDB » NodeJs » ReactJs » RESTFull APIs » VueJs » Python » Django

INTERMEDIATE: Javascript » jQuery » MySQL » Wordpress » Webpack

ADVANCED: BEM » Bootstrap » BulmaCSS » HTML5/CSS3 » Git/GitHub » Illustrator » Photoshop » SASS



PORTUGUESE: Native. ENGLISH: Level B1.